You look good.
You all free today?
Morning.
Ai's school has lapel pins?
When can I message you?
Yup.
I'll lose it.
I have a conference at 1:00.
Before noon works.
I'll bring my phone! Be in touch!
My school allows phones.
Don't copy my strongman.
This is cute.
Ai-kyun, your skirt's short.
Rika, wait.
It's your birthday.
Buy something you like.
Take this
and tell me about Daddy!
Don't tell me you're still hanging onto that.
He abandoned us. Do you really want to see him?
He abandoned you.
Why do you have to put it that way?
Listen, Rika, you won't understand this yet, but—
You stink like alcohol!
Leon will eat anything, even when he's small.
They seem carnivorous, though.
Mine is omnivorous too—
Yo!
Happy birthday, Rika!
Thanks.
We've got to celebrate.
It'll be Ai's not-a-shut-in party, too.
Talk about sudden. What happened?
I realized beating myself up
at home wouldn't solve anything.
"Beating yourself"? Whoa, kinky.
That's not what I meant!
Are you sure?
But was it all right?
Weren't you bullied?
It was fine, although I have no idea why.
Everyone seemed cautious
with me, maybe because I was out.
You call that "fine"?
Yeah, thanks to all of you.
Even if I'm alone at school, I have three friends outside.
You said it.
Yeah!
If anything happens, tell us.
If worse comes to worst, feed them to Leon.
They're essentially Haters.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Friends really are great, huh, Ai?
Tell us if you have problems too, Rika.
Sure thing.
I'm gonna make you listen to me grumble all day!
Grumble?
My flush of daddies.
You've got sugar daddies?!
As if!
One of these five is my real daddy.
So, which one is it?
Rika?
Don't you think this one's eyebrows look like mine?
Huh?
That said, even I don't know the answer.
Honestly, I'm not even sure he's one of these guys.
What do you mean?
I made a promise with this woman.
When I got into middle school, I could meet my daddy.
She promised, but...
Well, you see, I don't know either.
I'm preeetty sure it's one of these guys, though.
Don't make that face.
You're my genuine daughter. I gave birth to you.
There's no doubt about that!
That part pisses me off the most.
That's awful.
Right?
That woman can't stand the idea of me
meeting Daddy and getting along with him.
Why not?
She'll never allow me to be happy.
Because she's a tragic heroine with a persecution complex.
Stop.
You shouldn't insult your mom so much.
What? Aren't you on my side?
I am. That's why I'm telling you.
I don't want to trash talk my mother either.
But she's nothing like your moms.
She throws a fit when things don't go her way,
and all she tells me are half-assed lies.
She's never told me she's sorry for anything!
The only thing she does have is her damn pride.
She "should have been happier,"
even though it's her own fault.
So, she hates me, too.
Like she could have been happy if only she hadn't had me.
I'm sure she has her reasons, too.
Do you hate her as well?
Huh?
Isn't that what they call "codependence"?
If you don't make a clean break, nothing will—
Don't try to lecture me, goody-two-shoes!
I-I've had it!
Rika!
Gross.
I figured you'd chase after me, Ai.
I figured you wanted me to.
I'll join you.
Doing what?
Insulting our moms.
Don't force it.
I've got complaints, too.
Plus,
we're the Single-Mother Girls.
That's some name.
Ai.
Hm?
I'm Serious Rika right now.
So...
What was all that about, then?
I just remembered all the bad things at once.
It made it harder.
Right now, I hate my mom, too.
Lately, I've been wondering if I'll end up like her someday.
We'll be fine.
I guess.
Sometimes, adults seem like a different species!
Like, don't they get married and bang because they like it?
Is it because we're kids?!
I just
don't get it!
That was Rika, right?
She seems fine.
I wonder.
Don't worry. I'm sure she'll be back
to her usual self tomorrow.
Maybe I'm not cut out for female society.
Why not?
I can't help saying what I think.
What I think is logical and correct.
You're fine that way, Neiru.
I hate it when everyone just pretends to agree.
I don't know what it's like to worry about parents.
You get along with yours, huh?
I've never had either.
Huh?
It seems as if that spared me a lot of trouble.
The smallest one of all those lights is probably our bar.
Wow.
How often do you see your daddy, Ai?
Hmm... About once a month.
You're lucky.
Your mom doesn't take your daddy away.
He's still your daddy, even if your parents broke up.
Yeah.
I fantasize about mine.
All the more because I can't see him.
"A beautiful woman never needs a wallet."
His gentle voice is all I remember.
I can't... remember his face.
You'll meet him someday.
Someday.
I want to meet him now.
Now.
Moping over!
See you!
Thanks, Ai!
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Mannen!
Handle the Haters!
Teacher?!
So, this is today's assignment.
Thank goodness.
Now you'll be saved, too.
Huh?
You know Ikeda Clinic?
Yeah.
The old guy there is awful at giving shots.
Happy birthday.
Oh, Rika.
No way. That's awful.
Evening.
What? It's her birthday?
Yeah! Today's the day.
Welcome home.
Wow.
Rika!
How old is she?
Go ahead and eat your cake.
Drop dead.
No.
My little turtle, Mannen.
Redi.
Go back.
Your worries will go away.
All of them.
Every last one!
Who is this guy?
The teacher! He'll connect us to the cosmic truth!
Entrust everything to me.
Do so, and you will be saved.
Shove it, you old creep!
Take this!
Ow...
Piece of cake! All bark and no bite.
What have you done?! You attacked the teacher!
Teacher?
Of love, the universe, and the spiritual!
Huh?
Mom was in poor health, and Dad was struggling at work.
We were cursed by karma from our past lives!
So, we abandoned our attachments to the physical world!
We got rid of our house and money
so our whole family could connect to the cosmos!
Are you stupid?
You got swindled and then killed yourselves.
You suffer too, don't you?
What?!
Deep down, we're all the same.
All fixated on worthless appearances and hierarchies.
The haves grow arrogant; the have-nots grow envious.
Is this some kind of new-age lecture?
As if you don't cut yourself.
Erase yourself.
That will make it easier.
It can be easier?
Yes!
Acca, how is Rika doing?
Focus on your own battles.
I'm worried. She was crying.
She might be in a fix.
Ura-Acca.
Please!
Tell me what's happening!
Rika
gave up on fighting.
All those held in my arms are linked
to the mysteries of the cosmos.
You're still tense.
Don't worry.
See? It doesn't hurt, does it?
No.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Your tiny self can become part of a vast energy.
My tiny self...
You'll become one with the teacher.
There's no need to envy or hate anyone.
You'll erase your karma
and connect.
Could be nice.
No, that would be nice.
Rika!
Don't be fooled!
Ai?
Yeah.
And not just me. We're all here.
This isn't like you, Rika.
Are you going to let it end in a place like this?!
And what is "like me"?
Rika! Pull yourself together!
Rika, don't be fooled!
Rika!
Rika, say something!
Rika, hang on!
Rika!
I'm worn out.
Relax and surrender yourself.
That's right, Rika.
I was saved that way, too.
Yeah.
I want...
to be saved, too.
Will we lose one?
Looks like it.
Now, the hug of life!
Daddy...
Hmm?
Mannen?
What's that turtle doing?!
Don't interfere!
Mannen, you're supposed to deal with the Haters.
I get it.
He imprinted on me,
so he thinks I'm his mom.
And you've got to... protect your mom.
Rika!
Rika, come back!
Rika, please!
We're all here!
Mannen!
Rika!
That was close.
I almost turned into a selfish, piece-of-shit mother.
My mom taught me one true thing.
Men who ask women for money
are all fakes!
He's real!
The teacher is real!
He channels the cosmos!
Believe what you want!
Who cares
if he channels it
or scrambles it?!
Let's go, Mannen!
I'll knock you off your feet with a shot to the heart!
Whoa! You're heavy.
There, there.
But you're weak, too.
You cut yourself.
I am weak.
That's why I use this to balance so
I don't have to ditch things I care about.
I'm weak,
but that's the real me.
Even if it means hurting myself,
I'm going to live!
Rika!
Whoa.
This is the real "hug of life."
Rika.
Rika...
don't die.
Same to you.
Now! What should we do today?
What? What?
You're still awake?
I got hungry.
There's cake in the fridge.
I bet the cream's all dried out, though.
It really was the blink of an eye.
I got old before I knew it.
You're only 40.
Thirty-eight.
You're right. It is dried out.
I'm sure... you'll abandon me, too, Rika.
Yeah.
But not now.
I see.
To be continued.